like a seashell spell Alexander's preaching with a tan so divine sunscreen forgotten he's turning
to bright with a lobster people red and raw snapping our claws at the cosmic law
that his whispers the pot can't wait.
Alexander rises halo of foam.
Welcome my crustaceans to your new home.
We're the lobster people, red and raw.
Snapping our claws at the cosmic law.
People red and raw snapping our claws at the cosmic law
Kind of this morning, but I had so much fun doing it that I I decided I'd do it again, but in a different way
Okay
So I think I have more graphics handy this time where you go through each sign
We're gonna do some fun halloween
shizn't it
Okay, it's gonna be interesting things. There's gonna be a secret symbol. I'm gonna give you and there's gonna be a
Prophecy and there's gonna be a horoscope plus a full tarot card. So that's a lot of stuff
I've got to do 12 times 5 12 24 30 40 is that 60 things that they do so I will do that. Okay
This is gonna be fun
Everyone smile that oh, there's one person in the room. Well, well, well, what what opi are you in areas? Oh
You in areas
Oopie I saw your clip you clip me or you clipped on people talking about me. I like it. I didn't play the old intro
No, that was my newest thing at Red Tide Beach
But I oh you're leaving. Oh
Okay, are you a DJ Electra? You're an Aquarius. Okay, we're sitting with Scorpio today because I mean I started with
areas earlier. I'm going to start with Scorpio and Scorpio is not too far from from a query. It's okay.
Scorpio, Sagittarius, Capricorn queries. Okay, so we're gonna get there quickly. Oh, he's sneezing.
Okay, so let me check out
what they got for us.
Okay, do I got a score? Okay. So, okay, for Scorpio,
we had any Scorpios in the room. Oh, you really? Oh, okay. Well,
You're gonna have to wait for a while. You're gonna be late your last time to go daughter the Scorpio. Okay
So this will be interesting for anybody that knows the Scorpio. We're in Scorpio season, by the way
We are in Scorpio season
So I'm gonna just gonna put up this little picture of a scorpion. Let me see
Okay, there we go. We got a Scorpio season. Okay, so
What does psyche say? I wish I should do should I do some like I wish I had some like little like
spooky kind of like background stuff. I need to work on that. I'll put it on
later. For now, I'll just go like this.
That's the best I can do for you. Okay, Scorpios!
Are you listening? Okay, Scorpios. This is called the Serpent's Declipse.
So your next season opens up like a sealed tomb, Scorpio, mystery uncoiling under your tongue.
The next cycle demands that you face what you've hidden, not destroy it, but transform it.
Power is no longer about control. It's about clarity.
Something or someone returns, testing your loyalty to your own rebirth, the past clause for your attention.
We've already outgrown its grip.
You are the dark tide before dawn the alchemists of endings this year. Your magic is in the reveal tell the truth
Even if your voice shakes
So Scorpio your secret symbol for the season is the serpent's eye a spiral within a circle
symbolizing seeing through illusion while devouring fear and
The omen for Scorpios is when you dream of water turning to smoke know your transformation has begun
Okay
So Scorpio oh
My Scorpios, you know, I um, I started like having these visions of Lilith and Scorpio like right
You know at a certain time when I started making these videos and then I looked and it's like Lilith went right in Scorpio
Right when I started making those videos and so there's something to this stuff. Okay?
Okay
So
Next we have Sagittarius. Okay, so let me pull Sagittarius. Are you guys are you guys in like you guys like this?
I hope you guys like this. Yeah, I think this is gonna be interesting for you. Okay
We're going to Sagittarius. Do no one know Sagittarius people?
Sagittarius is the Archer. We know it's the Archer. It's like the
Cosmic
Centaur. Oh my goodness gracious. It's an easy
Okay
Well, okay here. I found a picture of it. Okay
There's a centaur
okay
For the Sagittarius, I have a prophecy and a horse for you
This is a little this is a little Halloween gift for everybody. Oh, I know after this I might hold the cards for me
That one's super cool. I forgot to include them in this presentation
but um
But you could take the symbolism. Oh you sneeze in clear. You sneeze in fun. Oh
Okay
So sad and serious
You are the archer's flame and so your your prophecy is this your arrow finds the unseen this season
Such a serious you've been running through a fog chasing meaning and chaos, but the horizon is finally clearing
What calls you now is an adventure for its own sake its purpose
The truth you seek won't come from another's mouth. It's in the echo of your own. You're being asked to teach through experience not through theory
Fire will test you, but it's your native tongue
Burn what's dull keep what sings?
I have an elemental omen for you and it really has to do with the fire in the sky, which I think is a storm.
When you hear laughter in a storm, your path has a line with destiny.
Okay, so that's like something to like an elemental omen is something that you you'll hear across
They'll be and so this confirms with something you you see or have seen
Right know that you're in line with your destiny your secret symbol is the phoenix arrow
It's a golden arrow encircled by smoke symbolizing the rebirth that comes when divide desire meets divine timing. Okay?
Next we'll do Capricorn, you know, I'm a Capricorn so I
I enjoy Capricorn stuff, okay?
Well, I'm still gonna put my Capricorn thing up.
Delete this, okay.
And green screen, Capricorn.
Oh, I'll just turn off the green screen, there we go.
There we go.
So that'll be the Capricorn it can be the horns on my head or something. I'll be behind my head here
I'll be the Capricorn. Okay. Any Capricorns?
For Capricorns
It's it's called the iron gate, okay
This portal might be some kind of iron gate, right, which is not necessarily a
gate
iron, you know, it's kind of like lower when low vibration, but
Listen though. Your climate's sacred Capricorn, but this year the mountain changed its shape.
The old summit, titles, trophies, the approval of ghosts, crumbles. You'll build new architecture,
one carved from authenticity instead of armor. The challenge is in endurance, its release. Power
will come when you let go of control and move with integrity instead of expectation.
Oh, pretty good. You're the keeper of sacred boundaries. Now learn to open the gate you guard
because we are on the guardian the earth gate, right? And so
Capricorn
our secret symbol is the black obsidian key the key that opens only
when our will aligns with truth and
The elemental omen we have to look out for is when a door shuts three times stop knocking
It was never your door. Oh
And it's kind of like,
oh, if you can like,
if here a door actually closed three times in a row,
that'd be weird, but then it's like,
that'd be like, no, it's like saying no.
But also, if you've shut the door on things something
three times, it was not your door.
I mean, just three times in charm, it didn't work, okay?
Now let's try 10 billion times.
So we have a short life here.
I mean, I'm gonna waste our life running after things.
So just, you know.
I'm not saying give up on things, but you know let things go it doesn't work out the first few times
You like the rose color glasses are you calling me Tony Stark? Who are you?
Tony Stark glasses look like they're those rose color. Hey money for 20. Okay. Okay, so that's oh my gosh
And so that was capital okay ready for Aquarius guys. I'll put up the Aquarius
Graphic
And you can see Aquarius.
OK, Aquarius, image file.
OK, Aquarius, of course, is the water bearer,
but it's not a water sign.
It's actually an air sign.
The water is going through the air.
It is ruled by Uranus and Saturn.
I do think about electricity a lot.
I think about, like, days of Aquarius,
I think about it's like now.
It's like when electricity is everywhere.
And it's like that electricity is the lightning
uses energy. Where is this Aquarius? Come on. I mean, come on.
Where are you? Aquarius.
Duh, duh, duh, duh. It must be this one.
Yes, okay.
Drop the link, Tony. Who are you, Vanguard?
Oh, I know you are Vanguard. No, I'm doing, okay, I'll do it, but you have to like, you know,
talk with me about horoscopes and stuff,
because we're in the middle of horoscopes right now.
Prophecies, okay, so we're doing a query is okay for queries. Here's what I have for queries. Oh
Dear queries
Hold on yes, okay, okay, so for course I have it's called the prism code
So Aquarius, your rebellion turns inward.
You've sparked change around you,
but the real revolution starts in your bloodstream.
Patterns break, people leave.
New frequencies hum beneath your skin.
Don't rush to define it.
This is the innovation of the soul.
The more you honor your difference,
the more you unlock collective healing.
Ooh, cause it's like, the queries are different,
but they never like, they always like to blend in
in a certain way, right?
Cause they're like, they're like everybody, right?
But then it's like, but they're so weird.
It's like it's gonna, everyone notices them.
They're also beautiful people.
Cause the world needs your weird, don't dilute it.
Secret symbol, the fractured prism.
Okay, it's a crystal split by lightning,
refracting infinite futures through one spark of insight.
Ooh, that's beautiful, okay.
And then we have an elemental element to look out for when light bends strangely through glass. Listen, it's your next idea calling your name. Okay.
So that's that. Okay. Aquarius. Capricorn Aquarius. Pisces. Okay. So now we have Pisces. Okay. Let me get up to fish.
You think that sounds perfect. Oh, great. Let's, uh, let's look at Pisces.
Um, do I have a two fish?
Well, just imagine these are two fish, okay
Because that was handy and I can see the Pisces. Just imagine that's Pisces. Oh, that should be Gemini. Oh, that'll be so good
Okay, but anyway, so for Pisces
This is the dream current it says you're crossing between realms Pisces the veil doesn't separate you it feeds you
but the line between empathy and exhaustion grows thin.
Learn discernment in the dream world.
Anchor your vision in the mundane
so your magic doesn't drown you.
The universe will whisper, but you must act.
You are both the tide and the tear, soft but unstoppable.
Okay, so secret symbol for you is the glass compass,
a transparent instrument that only works
when you trust your intuition, okay?
Your elemental omen is
When reflection move before you follow the ripple spirits already there
Okay
And so let's continue
To Aries
Aries is traditionally the first sign of a zodiac, but today Aries is going to be
in the middle of the reading, okay?
So Aries, of course, Aries is the RAM,
and pull it up.
We have a beautiful RAM's head here.
Let's tour, oh my gosh.
There we go.
Oh my God, I mean, there's so many signs.
Okay, I don't even know if I see it.
Is it this one?
Oh, it was paced.
Okay.
Well, I don't even see it.
I mean, I'll just have to put, I'll put this up.
This reminds me of Aries a little bit.
I don't know why it just kind of does.
Okay, but anyway, Aries likes to be first, okay?
Okay, so Aries is the Ember Crown.
The fire in your chest is an anger, it's initiation.
You've been sprinting through walls' areas,
but now the lesson is precision.
Not every battle is worth your blaze.
A quiet kind of courage will replace
the loud kind of victory.
You're the spark that begins revolutions,
but this year, we'll let spark with strategy burn clean.
For Aries, your secret symbol will be the Ember Crown,
three flames forming a trident,
symbolizing willpower guided by wisdom.
And your elemental omen,
when you see three lights flicker at once,
the universe is signaling your next breakthrough, okay?
Aries got to look out for that, okay.
Next we have Taurus, the boy, what's up Brandon Q?
We have Taurus the Bull, Taurus the Bull is right here.
Okay.
Taurus.
Okay, we have the Garden Gate.
It says, Taurus, the earth beneath your feet
hums louder this year.
What you planted is ready to rise,
but not everything deserves to bloom.
You've been asked to prune old attachments
and tend what really feeds your spirit.
Security isn't a cage, it's a rhythm.
Build beauty like it's your birthright. I
Have a secret symbol for you. It's the verdant spiral. It's a vine wrapped around a golden circle
representing steady evolution and sacred patience and
the environmental omen I have for you
Elemental omen I have for you is when a bird lands near you without fear something you've nurtured is ready to grow wings
Okay, I
Sometimes have birds almost land on my finger from you know, I just birds love me
Okay, now, hey, okay, hey, Brandon, okay, so now,
I'm looking for like twins, like this, you know, Gemini.
What should I do for Gemini?
Well, I just don't have it handy.
I'll just do like, keep it in Psyche right here.
There we go.
That's a Gemini because he the Gemini is it the air, right? Okay, it's a Gemini
The twin flame cipher. Oh, isn't it strange? I just like put like those the couple and I say with the twin flame
I really wasn't thinking about that, but things just happened like that
Okay, so there's two voices, one mission.
Gemini, you spent years echoing others.
Now your truth won't center stage.
Your mind's a labyrinth, but brilliance waits at its heart.
Choose words that heal, not just entertain.
Every sentence this year will ripple further
than you imagine.
Your secret symbol is the mirror feather.
Oh, look, and it's the meat,
like the Peterhead's feathers, right?
One half obsidian, one half quartz,
symbolizing duality as the divine design.
Ooh.
It sounds interesting. Maybe you want to get some obsidian and a feather, okay?
Elemental omen when you hear two people say the same phrase within an hour, the universe is speaking through repetition. Listen closely, okay?
Here we go. Next we have cancer. Any cancers in the house?
Guess we got kind of quiet. I don't know I guess but you know what I'm gonna have to slowly build my channel back
I guess not everyone's interested in music and you know astrology and mysticism and magic and all kinds of like really cool
Things that better than like screaming about beat all day
But you know if you're not interested in that maybe find another show and then hopefully I'll find people that aren't interested in it
That maybe got scared away when
It is her, you know
beat a screaming I mean all the time anyway so I'm sorry okay so Gemini are
we on Gemini yes I read Gemini have I read Gemini yes okay so next we have
cancer cancer cancer cancer cancer is a crab
They can be crabby, right not to be stereotypical, but they can be crabby
But they also like, you know, they're home their shell
Like to be pretty they're red. Okay. They're the lobster people to mind me a little bit of that. Okay
in South Park, they're the crab people.
So here's your prophecy, Cancer.
Your prophecy is the moon's vessel.
You're both ocean and tide, Cancer.
This cycle asks you to stop carrying
the shipwrecks of others.
Emotional mastery doesn't mean numbness,
it means navigation.
You'll rediscover your softness as strength,
but once hurt, we'll now heal through your hands.
Okay, your secret symbol is the silver shell.
A crescent cradling a pearl symbolizing empathy born of endurance.
That's a beautiful symbol.
And the elemental omen for you to look out for is when moonlight catches your reflection,
a forgotten part of you is ready to resurface.
Okay, watch the moonlight catch your reflection.
You ever see that like that beautiful like
Ethereal glow and like the fountain water under the moonlight
Okay, we've got a few more left I guess we got Leo just we got a lion here a lion right Leo
Okay, it's up there. Yep
Leo the solar heart your light has always drawn eyes Leo, but this year it draws allies
Hopefully not Ali master computer, but I like okay ego burns out purpose radiates
You'll shift from performance to presence from spotlight to lighthouse leadership isn't about being seen
It's about helping others see themselves
Shining a light on others, right?
Secret symbol of the lion's halo a circle of fire encasing a single eye
symbolizing illumination through compassion, and I love how I have a compassion
I think Leo's our compassionate people because it's a sun right and so there's compassion
but it's also like because the sun is like if it wasn't compassionate then it would just be out all
the time but it goes inside like 12 hours so it doesn't burn everybody too bad right and it's like
and then it's like it just gives them a nice like little little tan sometimes but anyway so
Someone unseen is blessing your eyes.
Ooh, have you felt that?
I felt that recently.
I almost suddenly get real hot in a cold night or whatever,
but it's like, sometimes it's uncomfortable,
but it's like, it's strange.
Okay, next we have Virgo.
We have the Virgo, the version.
Virgo, we're almost done and then I'll let you guys go
because I guess no one likes me anymore
because there's like six people here.
That's okay.
I'm gonna do what I wanna do and I'm having fun doing it.
So if there's one person.
I would appreciate it. They said hi, but you don't have to say hi. Okay. There we go. You have Virgo the virgin
okay, the one thing about Virgos is they're usually not very very virginic, but
That's another story. So Virgo the sacred measure you've built empires from order Virgo, but chaos has wisdom too this year
Let imperfection teach you grace. You're rewriting the idea of perfection not of flawlessness, but as linemen
what you fix outside must first be healed within.
Your symbol is a spiral compass,
an infinity loop crossing a ruler,
symbolizing the harmony between logic and intuition.
Your elemental prophecy is when plans collapse
and peace follows, the divine has just edited your blueprint.
Okay, that's like a tower.
Sometimes there's a tower
and it's like instead of like being a bad thing,
it's like, oh my God, everything's peaceful and beautiful now.
It's like, that happens sometimes to me.
Okay, well, we got Libra and that's Libra is it.
So, okay, I'm gonna put up the scales
and then I'm gonna let you go
because I guess nobody wants to hang out with me anymore.
So, it's okay.
It's okay.
Well, if you could like this stream
and then maybe share it and tell your friends.
Oh, my friend did these really cool horoscopes, okay
You don't have to that'd be cool
Okay, what's the last time?
Libra, right?
Libra
Libra, or are you there? Okay
Okay guys this the end, okay
Libra at the veiled scale
So, here's your prophecy, Libra.
The balance you crave will come not from pleasing others,
but from daring to tip your own scales.
Libra, this is the year you choose.
Harmony born from honesty, not compromise.
You'll find beauty and contrast and peace and decision.
Your secret symbol is the opal feather,
a white feather balanced on a blade,
symbolizing truth as a softest weapon.
Elemental Omen. When two paths appear equally lit, pick the one that scares you. It's the real equilibrium.
Okay guys, so now the circle is complete. I've done, you know, Scorpio through Libra 12 symbols forming a hidden zodiac wheel of awakening.
Okay.
So maybe I have something else planned for you. Like a wonderful nose.
Song I can play later about this whole this whole prophecy. Oh
Oh, wait a minute guests is a guest
There are guests coming up is it a such a thing a porn bomb. What's going on here? I don't believe it. There's no guests here. I
Don't get guests anymore. Who is this? This is a prank
Who is it?
Vanguard
Hello
Hello there, psych. How you doing fella? Oh
I'm okay. How are you doing it my?
Me I told you about
Come on aquariums. I am the goat of all aquariums in the goat
Well, I'm a capricorn, so I'm very much a goat, but I'm a capricorn Aquarius. I'm like I'm winning Aquarius
and Mars and Aquarius all in the first house, and so.
So, can you ask, where did you buy your Tony Stark glasses
and why are they so rose colored?
Why are they rose colored?
I don't know, maybe because I think they're more orange,
but it's like they just kind of like,
everything's like kind of red
because I have these red blinds
and then with the purple behind me.
And yeah, I got them from, you know,
Tony Stark Industries, special pitch order.
Um, have they got metta bullshit inside?
Um, like metta inside of them? No
The only four letter word associated with these glasses is Timu, T-E-M-U
Whoa
Timu, U-S-A, nice one
Timu, Timusa
You know they used to there's a place in Japan called Usa and I used these to ship from Japan from the Usa port
I would say made in Usa, but it would people think it says USA, but it was actually from Japan
well
So why would why why were you disappearing?
I was only late coming to the party because haven't you streamed in a while and it took everything off my avatar
So I have to go through it again and set it up
Yeah
It's going through growing pains. Well, I guess maybe because you changed your computer or you're logged out or cleared your case cash or something
No, no, no put it this way the stream yard I used last week isn't the stream yard I'm using now
Yeah, because they added a bunch of stuff like you know
They've added all these new sound effects and so it might have pushed away your old sound effects
And like they put all these old these new images and stuff and like
the backseat yes I don't know you have a very limited I think it's a very limited amount of
stuff you can put in the backstage even as a paid member I'm kind of like I don't like
continually running out of stuff. The only avatar I was allowed was my Google avatar
and I'm having to go find a few avatars to come over here. Yeah it's a bit wrong isn't it?
Well it means you but it's fun to create new avatars I love creating new avatars.
My business
You know about artificial intelligence don't tell me
You come on. Oh, I generate it with it with input and I think it's one of the one of a kind based on my input
Is there's never been another one in the world? It's pretty crazy. I'm here. It is look actually when it was been through a couple things here
There you go
Perfect
Doesn't look good
No, I can't see jack shit. You can't see it
Well, apart from the stuff you always put about psych verse fucking eyes and fucking stupidness
Well, you don't see the fire the letter phi and you the crescent moon the eye the star with like the
You know probably the flea and around it
Nora and a menorah missing two prongs go fuck yourself and
I need a fire, a fire, a philosophy, a psyche, bye
Say hi, it's Greek, you know
Me it's me it's me whether I said it was a menorah listening to prom
I don't know. Maybe I think a lever is would find a track
All the stars are in the wrong place at the wrong time
In your perspective because thinking about a Hubble telescope takes a picture of a galaxy, but that's from one angle of it
What if what if you take it from a different angle like a billion short light years away?
It's probably look like a different thing
Hello, is that true? I don't know. Maybe I'm wrong
Please tell me you know the Sun is a star don't you psych?
Yeah, it's a little dwarf star, right
What the Sun's a dwarf star dwarf isn't in a white dwarf?
No, it's not
I'm gonna look up. I'm gonna look up in the thing real quick. Hold on. Is it guy? Can you tell me the Sun is a white dwarf?
You're telling
Terran our solar system has a white dwarf. What yeah, our mother is a white dwarf
No, it's not Milky Way. Yeah, not it made
Imaginary diamond two feet tall
That is like basically our
Fall off
And he's about to say he's about to say it's some some something have a white dwarf somewhere along the line
No, we don't live in a white dwarf solar system
Psych full stop right now is the Sun a
white
Dwarf
It says no the Sun is not a white dwarf. It is a yellow dwarf. Oh
Yellow dwarf star. I'm sorry. I got the color up a little bit
So it says white dwarfs are the dense dead cores of stars that have already finished their main life cycle while the sun is still in this main sequence
using hydrogen and dehalium and will eventually become a red giant before the final stage as a white dwarf
it turns into a red giant from a white dwarf isn't this like it's like game of thrones
it's like you know they have like a little white dwarf and it turns into a big red star dragon right and then it's like
Wow, I don't know how you're getting equating red dwarfs to this analogy, but
Well, it says they turn to assemble eventually turn into a red dwarf. It says
Right, did I say red dwarfs? I mean fucking don't use the Giants
Red giant white Dorp in a red giant
Looks like a game of chess with the very disproportionate pieces
Well, anyway, do you know what type of star beetle juices?
Yeah, it's the armpit of Orion, isn't it?
Well...
Hello? Vanguard?
I'm still here.
The armpit of Orion, let's just say this Beetlejuice
is about to go supernova.
Hold on one second. It's what?
About to go supernova.
It is.
Ew, I was just looking at this woman,
I was looking at like, you know,
Beetlejuice, meaning armpit.
Oh, it's Beetlejuice, the fucking star, ya ballad.
I know, no, but I got this picture of this woman
like making it as an armpit.
Can't miss Wow
It sounds like we're different ends of the spectrum at the moment
I think I think so I think that's been verified. No, I thought Beetlejuice was the star
Beetlejuice star is like the armpit of Orion. Let me and I'm gonna prove it to you. Oh, right
Yeah
Look at it. Look at it. Look at it. Look at it. Look at it. Look at it. Look at where it is. Look at the Beetlejuice star.
Hold on. I'm turning off my, my, my, uh, back.
Oh, yeah.
Beetlejuice.
Thank God. Let me just prove something to you, okay?
Mr. Know-It-All, hold on a second.
Okay.
You think you know everything, and you laugh at me, but look.
What did I say?
Look at what you're laughing at.
His armpit. Look. There's...
There's Orion. There's his armpit. Yeah. Yeah. You know, just feel just like I said, I don't know everything, but they're
Bealjuice is the closest star that's about to go bang very soon. Yeah, man. Well, he should
worm better deodorant. Is that why they have secret? If it hasn't gone already because it takes so
I don't know just beside me already said his name several times and now that knowing Michael Keaton Keaton character is probably gonna come
annoy us
Thanks a lot
Wow
I remember he's a very annoying character
But how many years is a BG away from us?
A BJ? I'll give you one in 25 minutes if you can get here now.
I didn't want to say it third time, so
how many light years is BJ when it goes supernova from us?
I don't know, but if Betelgeuse, a red supergiant star, replaced our sun,
its enormous size would engulf everything up to Jupiter's orbit.
Every planet from Mercury to Mars and even parts of the asteroid belt
would lie inside the star.
So, Bill Juice, I did see it a third time, it's the closest star to us, but apparently
it's the closest star that's going to go bang, supernova, yeah man.
Well what does that have to do with us?
I mean you know what supernova means don't you?
The champagne supernova in the sky is that a song in it from your land, England a champagne supernova
I didn't know you loved the way she's there my fucking more yummy
Said maybe you're gonna be the one that saves me
Any way I wonder all Vanguard
Hey
Is it the end
Hey, it can explode any time this happens over here. He is bright as a quarter moon
I don't know very much. I don't love very much. You don't look at his armpits on fire basically, okay?
And then I will say
In American fucking overreach
Fuck you
That about your point and you're screaming right over me the entire times
No, I was talking in them. I was trying to comment and you over talk me. It's what let me talk
It's my show if you want to talk about your show you get a show
See what I mean
I mean champagne supernova Beetlejuice in the sky fuck
It's been a nightmare all I have is
You know, bad 80s movies and Oasis albums in my head right now.
Okay, but anyway, okay, so it says.
If Betelgeuse, or you play the Star of the Sun, okay, I already read that one, okay.
It says, the star Betelgeuse have a longs to Orion constellation at the end of the
stages of its life.
It can explode at any time.
When this happens, it will appear as bright as the quarter moon in the sky, sufficient
to cast shadows.
It is so massive that it may turn into a black hole or a neutron star.
If that, if it turns into a black hole, it will become the closest black hole to Earth.
Ooh.
Mm-hmm. I thought I thought I thought Rosie O'Donnell was the closest black hole to the earth. Well, yeah. Oh
That's just something as big as the plug. Hey the Romans out Beetlejuice is a bright yellow star instead of the red super giant
It is now. Oh the Romans. I don't believe anything they say
Anyway, you want to see it artists interpretation of Beetlejuice
Does it have many heads in so many strands of a name like Beetlejuice, Beetlejuice, Beetlejuice?
No, it looks like a pumpkin head demon more, because it had the big sun head and it's running through the space.
See, it has a tail.
I don't know, it looks really good.
It looks really good.
If blogger was to look through his armor,
it would look like something they just created.
Yeah, I get it.
But that's not actually an observation.
It's still an artistic representation
from the thermal and other data
they can go and receive.
Excuse me?
It's not a photograph.
This is a picture from outer space.
It is real.
It's not a picture. It's not a picture. It's a picture. It's a picture.
What's this they're ever going to get?
Photograph. No, it's not.
You had to take a picture of the sun. I mean, the flash.
Come on.
That's not a picture of the sun.
What?
It's a picture of the star.
but the sun is now we started to represent it in an artistic representation
that artisan what are you saying the Hubble telescope isn't real what are you crazy
mate hobo telescope can't even see it like that so what the fuck are you talking about
fuck off how about um what about the james web experience
Well, the James Webb cannot even see it like that either
First of all the James Webb telescope doesn't take pictures it just
All right, are you talking about let's just say what life of women and we want to talk about
Are you married or have you been alone for years and years?
You've you here. I've been alone for years and years. So tell me what you think with your green screen behind yet
You need to get out you need to find a woman and stop yelling
I've entertained more women than you've had hot dinners in my life
But probably I mean if a how old are you like a hundred? I mean it's like you sound like an old man
I'm very old
I am the goat of all aquariums
Well, I am too because I'm a capricorn Aquarius
No, you don't get the goat reference dear
The goat god goat stands for God like you know, yeah, it doesn't go to stands for the greatest of all time
Well, that's like a that's like a boomer thing. I mean, that's like goat stands for like, you know, originally a goat
I mean, yeah, we can make an acronym like sleep for like basketball players. That's gonna bum. But no, no, no
Oh, yeah
Patrick you only know your palm and your five sisters Patrick. We know that
Out of this I have so many women my life. I don't need them every day
In my life. What if you didn't have it harmed who would do that for you?
Can I do it for you? I'd come out there and do it for you if you needed me to.
Yeah, mate. You couldn't do anything for me.
Yes, I could. I'd blindfold you and I'd put on my blonde wig and, you know, spit it with my hands and go to work.
I wouldn't even let you wipe my arse, Pearl Harbor.
I wouldn't want to do that. I mean, you'd have to pay for like a nurse to do that. I just do the sexual stuff. I'm not into that scat plate.
Right. Let me put it another way. I wouldn't let you and LD anywhere near me, Pearl Harbor.
Alright. Would you rather have me and LD as your nursing team or Jimmy Sabo?
None of the above. Well, you have to have either Jimmy Sabo or LD and me and I'm sick.
Oh, no, no, no. I've earned enough in life to say no, I don't accept your fucking three choices.
Fuck off, man. How about like F. Marie Keele, LD, me and Jimmy Sabo?
None of the above.
None of the above I mean that's I mean it's a kind of like you have to answer the question because it's like a game
You have to marry an F and you have to answer anything
Would I marry you mate mate? I'm not gay to start with but you seem like you have a bit of a spell in
It likes attention. You're an attention whore.
Why did I want to marry an attention whore?
A attention whore?
What the fuck?
I heard another voice there. Is LES there?
Wow, attention ho, attention ho, psych is an attention ho, oh dear, with a cosy butt.
I'm having been being harassed by this guy, he's calling me a whore, I feel very insulted.
Have you heard of the whore of Babylon in Vanguard and tell me what you think the whore of Babylon means?
The whore of Babylon. Babylon. Yeah, what do you want to know about the whore of Babylon? Who is it? What does she represent today?
Well, do you know where Babylon is? New York? No
Isn't there a Babylon New York? Yes, I believe there is.
Well, you see what I mean? There's no point continuing with this conversation. Oh, you're talking with the original Babylon. Oh, yeah
Well, it doesn't it's in Iran, right, but it doesn't exist anymore. All right. No
More like Iraq
Iraq, okay. Well, they're very close together. I mean, it's like it was a big big
Well, glad to see Iraq and not Iraq. Okay. Fuck
How about after you see Afghanistan as I pronounce it and
Kuwait quit quit quit Kuwait while you're ahead
We buy your head Donald Trump's felt Kuwait
While you're ahead Donald Trump's felt in your bunch of fucking war mongering cuts
How did you figure that out you're I mean you're so good
Never mind. I'm just kidding. I'm not Donald
I'm not Donald Rumsfeld nor not Rudy Giuliani or George Bush or dick
I swear to God. So what type of coffee are you drinking? Is it McDonald's cheap shite or what?
No, it's like um, it's um from a bagel store, and it's like I go and it's like unlimited coffee
It's Jewish coffee. Yeah, it's Jewish because it's free
So what do they call that the knack bar roast or what?
No, no, it's just called a bagel. It's called the Einstein because it's brilliant. It's a brilliant system
What I mean I'm dead. I call themselves Einstein's fucking coffee. What you know Einstein was just Picasso in a silly wig
So with Salvador Dali
Donald Trump. No, but he was someone else. He was like, I think he was he was a Betty Davis and
Whatever I would have a baby Jane. I think I was he played that part
Anyway, how's your cop doing? I
Have several cats which one I have. Let's see. I have Rudy right here. Would you like to say hi to Rudy?
Well, is Rudy quite rude?
Yes, he's very rude. He's red as well Rudy. Are you rude?
He's rude
Here, come on. Say hi to Vanguard.
Oh, I have Vanguard. I'm ready.
Oh, he sneezed.
Good boy. So, Vanguard. Okay, I just want your opinion. Do you like me better like this or like this?
Do I like you better like what or what? Do you like me better like this or like this?
Um, can you put a bag over your head and then then I might comment
Um, I don't have a bag that would fit over my head
Can you make sure it's the bagel coffee bag, please
Doesn't fit but it is a nice hat
Hello
I think I lost some
No, that's a fucking keeper we need to keep that can I clip that and I don't do that
No, I'm not pretending. It's a yarmulke. It's actually my own design of a hat
It's like more like, you know, like a
Frigian cap, you know, paper bag. I
Need to just you need to color it red and then it'll be perfect. Oh
You're a good sport. You're a good sport. You're actually a good sport. Like you're a good sport a good sport. Well, what game do you want to play hide the sausage?
I've told you, I'm not a homosexual mate.
It's okay, we don't, it doesn't have to be gay, you know, it's just like, you know, you just like,
experiment, experiment once in a while.
You said you're not married, right?
I'm not a homosexual mate.
Just explore yourself.
It didn't work with women. Maybe it's time for me. I think you just need to try it with me
Could you stop it on people being a fellow?
You like to move in with me and marry me
Okay, so I'll show you my photograph
As long as you're nude in it. Oh my god, you look like the penguin
You look like oh my gosh if you look like Danny DeVito, I'm not interested anymore. I'm sorry. I'm more interested in like you know
Even like the Alfred or even like that Christopher walk in better than Danny DeVito. I mean Danny DeVito is creepy. I'm sorry
Vanguard it won't work out this lifetime
Indeed will agree to disagree into
Give a cat woman outfit
That'd be interesting to see you wear.
Hello, oh you're still there.
So, can you ask, can you ask, do you live in section eight public housing?
Oh, well, you know, that's why I'm on the streets right now because all the,
all my funding has been cut off from the government and so I'm completely out of luck.
So you live in you don't live in section eight public housing you live in a motel
Well, I don't know where I don't know but it's like all I know is that the police haven't come and dragged me out of here yet
That's a song. That's all I know. That's all I really think about, you know
Yeah, I'm saying this water right thank fuck you're not Mexican descent
Why then I'd have like a wonderful, you know dinner it probably have you know
Have you seen what the feet of torture victims in Guantanamo be? Oh, I don't try to think about this thing
I don't want to think about but what are you talking? I don't want to be disgusting stop it
All right, that's not they don't do that to Mexicans, please
Guantanamo be
you know they're doing the landscaping they don't they're not the prisoners please
they're like doing masonry they're you know they're um yeah that's one of the torture things
is they play mariachi band until the person like you know jumps out the window but so um
What on the other side of where Cuba?
Well, it's better than what yeah Cuba isn't that great they have great cigars
Great food
Wow
Are there beautiful beaches there? It's an island, isn't it?
Yeah
Get more information get more information get more information
Get Mo
What are you talking about you don't make any sense you're talking in circles. Oh
Get Mo I get keep going on. Oh, anyway, so Vanguard I mean
I'd give anything to do except to just laugh at my face the entire show. I mean come on
I'm trying to have a laugh and are you laughing at me? You're just laughing at my face
What it's better than fucking drama isn't it I
Don't I don't think so. I'm when I'm drama at least I'd like 40 people in the chat now. I have hardly anybody here
No problem. No problem. No problem. Oh, it's not your fault. It's my fault. It's my I've I've dropped the ball
Hey, everybody vanguards in the chat everyone. I'm gonna get in the chef
No, my problem. Why are my numbers higher? They should be higher with you in the chef
You have you're the you look like the penguin. I mean, it's like they should at least like you know like you for that
See anyway, I did come up, but I was doing my shit to understand what's going on with stream yachts
I did appear now. I'm about to disappear, but uh, no
Well, are you always running up running off? Where you go? Where are you going? So secretive?
What?
Where are you being so secretive? What are you? What are you hiding?
I've gotta go work on that one's next move
What are you doing? Where are you going? What are you doing this in this 5d chess game?
I thought I would go bat mom's next move, huh?
Hey, do you know what I have a penguin fetish?
Do you really?
Can I
Patrick Patrick kills any numbers Patrick. You're a fucking arsehole
You have a niche
Patrick I mean Patrick no York with a piece of your umbrella in my butt, please
Release the gas
The Houston and Genic gas. Please.
I just want to try that one.
Patrick Papa, you mentioned his name.
He was desperate.
He was so desperate for somebody on panel
to mention his name.
He goaded me in to mention Patrick from New York
with a B symbol who's a fucking magamaniac.
You're talking about me?
Oh, no.
I can never win.
I thought you're talking about me finally and then he's talking about Patrick in the chat. Oh, no
Everyone I was Pat now I'm Pat Pat V
No, I guess it means Pat the fifth or Pat victory or something like that. I don't
Where did you get that white wig? I
Is my natural hair color? Oh
Go fuck yourself. You all busted
Where did I get it? Where did I get where do I get everything either McDonald's or T-Mobile?
I mean, there's only two places. They even shop anymore
Well, you're not gonna live long are you?
No, I'm not I'm already living way past my my expectancy
I'm not happy about it
Me to make sure you start shopping in dollar general
You'll make your exit very quicker. Where do you buy your tampons?
Hello, I
Mean your adult diapers
Do you wear adult diapers?
Well, are you asking me why I wear up by my shit rule my yeah, where do you yeah, what do you what do you wipe your butt with?
bug rule
With what buckle of a bug?
bug rule bug rule
bug rule
Okay, well, I'm not sure what that is, but can you send me a carton of it?
What I'm tired of wiping with my hand
Make sure it's your right hand. They're not your left hand. Yeah, why wait that would not be like Indian style
Hey, you know what I'm actually a vegan Patriots long-lost sister. Can I move in with her, please?
Do you know vegan Patriot give a connection with vegan Patriot, please I might need to go stay with her for forever
but
Do you think she would mind her long-lost sister?
I've got fuck all this here both I
RL IP to community when it comes to vegan also, you know, she is you know exactly who she is
How'd you know she is so fast?
the exact same reason I know who Alexander Mears is and I talked to her
long before you ever did yeah well did you have a rendezvous just ask Jimmy
Which I definitely want to draw with me and Jamie's Cowboys if she wants to
So are you still best friends with Alexander Mears?
We're on a break
It didn't take long did it
What's what's wrong?
That did not take long at all
It's so funny
Why are you laughing you can you're laughing at me again over over at something completely different like is there so many things
If I like made you at least in you giggle. I'm just I was just kidding. I didn't
I'm just kidding. I don't I don't want to have us. I don't want to have a monogatron with anybody
Nothing was like, you know, Christine Aguilera and little Kim
And the rest of that whoever was singing that song
How long is the break been going so far from our 15 days of our 30-day no contact?
yeah
And how much does it cost for your Jewish lawyers in between?
Well, I figured out that my sister's Jewish so I save a lot on legal fees
a 30-day no contact well yeah it's a it's not going well it's I've already
broken up with beta I mean it's like well I quite like be about it well you
would wouldn't you well I quite like Iran quite like her what Iran oh you're
And
I do like
She's not gonna ruin all the Persian people for me
Iran's not got nuclear missiles only like a country of nine million people who has
I know I know but but Iran is like a you know
It's it's I love it used to be called Persia and I used to have a lot of Persian friends. They're very you know
Wow, I see people and
unfortunately
this one I
Don't know what she wants to do. She she wants to make make my ears bleed by
Screaming at me 24-7. So I'm taking myself out of the equation. So when you circumcised as a Jewish person
Yeah, but I'm but I'm a Goyam, but I'm still circumcised. I don't know. It's very fucking funny
You know what a Goyam is. You're definitely Jewish, aren't you? Yeah, I
Mean a Sparta, I mean a Goyam. Oh dear
Yeah, and did you follow the Talmud or the Torah?
Well, you know the Talmud is the oral tradition and so
You know, you know the Torah is like the five books that like everyone falls, you know
But I think the Talmud is actually the where the real information is but it was the oral tradition
So it's like a lot of it is
Where all the real information is I'm glad you said that that's where they say that Jewish people can rape anybody as long as not
Jewish people they can I don't believe that
It's all it's a translation, I think there's some things put in there for shock value or something like that, you know
I was pushing up the limits of every right
Oh, yeah, did I overstep the mark mentioning the Talmud and its correct purpose?
Yeah, the Talmud is a great book. It talks about, you know
You know marry the hairdresser. It talks about Jesus burning an excrement in hell. It's interesting book
Oh, it also says that anybody who's not Jewish is a cunt
Well luckily I'm a Jewish. I mean never mind. I'm not Jewish
Whoa
Awkward
I'm just kidding. I don't I don't I don't know, you know, who knows what we are. I think we're all everything, right?
I think we're all
Everything I mean, I do love a good potato pancake. I love the hash brown at McDonald's. I love
No, there's a little chocolate coins that are good. I like
you know
Adrenal made of clay. I like
extra holidays. I
like
You know comedy I like Hollywood show business
You know
Basically everything Jewish. Do you like Mossad?
No comment
I like Massimo, the clothing brand.
I like music, most sick, music.
I don't know the other words you were saying.
Makes me sad.
I didn't think I could get more sad than this.
I'm sorry.
Hey, hey with the monkeys. I'm a monkey. I'm a capricorn monkey. I want to see it. Do you want to see a video with Vanguard?
No, I'm quite sick and tired of seeing your EI bullshit. You must add support up. You get obviously seven
Okay, that didn't go well like I just said
Maybe I shouldn't dance around with
Lunatics, okay, I'm gonna play video anyway. Yeah
Vanguard you're gonna need to maybe take a step back listen to this song. It's all about kindness
Untouchable, spinning lives like you're invincible
But every tear you shed on someone else
Is the shadow cast upon yourself
We live through each other, breathing the same air
Every cut, every bruise, every whisper, this prayer
The world is a mirror, reflecting your hand
The pain you give is the pain you'll understand
So try life
Love is what grows
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Cool tables, bright lights, captain of the game
What's your glory fades, leaves only shame
Exaggerated laughs, your drama's crown
But the world turns quiet when you tear others down
You build walls to feel bigger inside
But the cracks you make nowhere to hide
The pain you've sewn, the hearts you've scarred
Is the echo in your own back
Tread, gentle, let empathy reign
We are one in the joy, one in the pain
What you give is the world, what you take is your part
Treat others like you was the
It's the lowest point you do find people that stay.
Yeah. Chat friends forever you want that one?
You got it.
I think this is it.
Okay, hold on I think we have to go get it from the elsewhere
It's not moving. Oh my gosh.
I had to throw some. Okay.
Oh my gosh, what's going on here?
Got it throwing shade ziggie putting on the show
Rans laughing while JT's got receipts with circus clowns
and digital seats
Midnight chats and pixel fights trolls and army on nights ban hammer swing, but I still say hi
Cuz chaos
When it's amplified
Chad friends forever, flying monkeys on the wire
Slinging memes in gasoline, we set the stream on fire
Yeah, we fight like thunder, then laugh till sunrise
You drive me crazy
But you're my tribe
Ziggy drops a diss track, ran lights and smoke
God, he says something evil, maybe just a joke.
J.T.'s in the corner, dropping prophecy lines.
Meanwhile, I'm the priest of this circus divine.
Trans forever
Very great song classic
I was just as lost as you
Don't flinch I've got the scar
I'm marching out of the dream, slow, quiet
do you still hear me? I don't know. A few more people here live so I'll play one more and I'll say goodbye.
I'll say
your gift they laughed when I fell but I danced in the dirt every scar I got just
rewrote my worth all I ever wanted was to free my fear
Blessing the dark, praising the blue The night is the canvas where visions move
So
Thank you for being here it's a little bit too too depressing with like nobody coming here anymore, so
Maybe I was shadow banned maybe
Yeah, I need your help guys to
But people know I'm still around. I'm not such a bad dude. Okay. Thank you. I love you.
Adoo. Au revoir. Au revoir, Pee Wee.